(Sheldon(on phone):)Tell me another interest of yours.
Oh, I'm sorry. I have no desire to get
in the water till I absolutely have to.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Tell me another interest of yours.
- Uh-oh, he's stuck in an infinite loop.
- I can fix it.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
(Sheldon:)It's interesting but isn't ventriloquism
by definition a solo activity?
Yeah. Tell me another interest of yours.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Is there any chance you like monkeys?
Yeah, what is wrong with you?
(Sheldon:)Everybody likes monkeys.
(Sheldon:)Hang on, Kripke.
A loop counter and an escape
to the least objectionable activity.
(Sheldon:)Howard, that's brilliant.
(Sheldon:)I'm surprised you saw that.
(Howard:)Gee, why can't Sheldon make friends?
All right. That last interest strikes me
as the least objectionable.
(Sheldon:)And I would like to propose
that we do that together.